<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Silent Librarian</title><link>https://thesilentlibrarian.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on The Silent Librarian</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© {year}</copyright><atom:link href="https://thesilentlibrarian.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Terminal</title><link>https://thesilentlibrarian.github.io/terminal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 20:31:07 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://thesilentlibrarian.github.io/terminal/</guid><description> const term = new Terminal(); term.open(document.getElementById('terminal')); term.write('This console is not working yet. Please use the chrome console.')</description></item><item><title>ROX Refine Step Simulator</title><link>https://thesilentlibrarian.github.io/rox-refine-step-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 22:31:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://thesilentlibrarian.github.io/rox-refine-step-simulator/</guid><description>Summary This page contains the step-by-step refinement simulator for Ragnarok X. You may use this for reference before conducting real refinement inside the game, or just for fun.
&amp;ndash; Note: the crystal cost is only estimation for white 2h weapon, excluding repair cost. For blue weapon, multiply with 2. For gold weapon, multiply with 4.
Refine Step Simulator Current Level Refine Reset History count upgrade: 0 count downgrade: 0 count failed: 0 count damage: 0 total cost: 0 # Result From Lv To Lv Crystal Cost .</description></item><item><title>ROX Repeated Refine Simulator</title><link>https://thesilentlibrarian.github.io/rox-refine-simulator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 15:32:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://thesilentlibrarian.github.io/rox-refine-simulator/</guid><description>Summary This page contains the refinement simulator for Ragnarok X. In this game, refining equipment has a variable chance to upgrade, failed, damage, and even downgrade. This simulator helps conduct a controlled experiment on this refinement mechanism, producing a report that may or may not be valuable for making refinement decisions inside the game.
For step-by-step refinement simulator, click here.
Simulator Input Parameters To use the simulator, please input the experiment parameters.</description></item></channel></rss>